Hamidullo Saydullaev Eront-End dovolor

Front-End developer

+998907636669

github/in/here

linkedin.com/in/here
x5292623@icloud.com

Profile

Currently, I'm a young & talanted and raising Frontend developer.

If take a look my background, you'll probably see always working and learning
In my early ages, spent my time to be perfect in every field. Unlike others, I chose a school that is specialized for English & Math & Computer Science.

I tried get all knowlede with perfect and attention so, Up to this date not loosing my motivation for study, still continue learning.

Education

Udemy Academy

Frontend development

May 2021- Sep 2021 (Anticipate)

iCode Academy

Frontend development

Oct 2021 - Apr 2022 (Anticipate)

Skills

Development

HTML5 • CSS3/SASS • Bootstrap •
Javascript • React JS • React Hooks • Redux
• Webpack • Gulp • NPM • Git/Github • Rest
API • Rest ful API • MUI • Taildwind CSS •

Languages

- English Conversational
- Russian Conversational
- Uzbek Native or Bilingual

Work Experience

Digital City of Andijan

Front-End developer internship

Apr 2022 - Present

Worked with senior developers on Frontend development for user interfaces and functions.

I'm responsiable for user interfaces and working with API's. I was one of lider of our developement team.

Upwork

Frontend developer

Apr 2022 - Present

I did a lot of small jobs on the upwork platform and improved my coding skills.